final dataQ = [
  {
    "question": "What is the capital city of Saudi Arabia?",
    "A": "Jeddah",
    "B": "Riyadh",
    "C": "Dammam",
    "D": "Mecca",
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "question": "In which year was Saudi Arabia founded?",
    "A": "1902",
    "B": "1912",
    "C": "1932",
    "D": "1952",
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which desert covers most of Saudi Arabia?",
    "A": "Gobi Desert",
    "B": "Sahara Desert",
    "C": "Thar Desert",
    "D": "Rub' al Khali (Empty Quarter)",
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the official language of Saudi Arabia?",
    "A": "Arabic",
    "B": "Urdu",
    "C": "English",
    "D": "Turkish",
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the currency of Saudi Arabia?",
    "A": "Riyal",
    "B": "Dinar",
    "C": "Dirham",
    "D": "Pound",
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the main religion practiced in Saudi Arabia?",
    "A": "Christianity",
    "B": "Hinduism",
    "C": "Islam",
    "D": "Buddhism",
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which holy city in Saudi Arabia do millions of Muslims visit annually?",
    "A": "Medina",
    "B": "Jeddah",
    "C": "Mecca",
    "D": "Taif",
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "question": "Saudi Arabia is known for being the world's largest exporter of what resource?",
    "A": "Natural gas",
    "B": "Coal",
    "C": "Petroleum (Oil)",
    "D": "Gold",
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which Saudi Arabian city is known as the 'Gateway to the Two Holy Mosques'?",
    "A": "Jeddah",
    "B": "Riyadh",
    "C": "Medina",
    "D": "Mecca",
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which body of water lies to the west of Saudi Arabia?",
    "A": "Arabian Sea",
    "B": "Red Sea",
    "C": "Persian Gulf",
    "D": "Mediterranean Sea",
    "answer": "B"
  }
];
